A Guide to the Virginia Miscellany Papers, 1657-1931
Library of Virginia
- Legal papers, 1657-1862 (Box 1-2)
  - Legal Papers, 1754-1755 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bond, 31 July 1754, Nathaniel Gist, Junior, of Augusta County to Richard Pearis., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 24 December 1754, Thomas Caton to Alexander Brown and Company., 1 leaf.
    - Order, 21 January 1755, John Nash to Captain Robert Stewart, concerning payment of an account to Mrs. Barbara Jones., 1 leaf.
    - Order, 28 January 1755, John Whitman to Captain Robert Stewart, concerning payment of an account to Mrs. Barbara Jones., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 30 October 1755, George Holoback to Lenox and Scott., 1 leaf.
    - Judgment, 21 November 1755, Augusta County Court in Benjamin Borden v. William Todd., 2 p., copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1756-1757 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Narratio, [1756], Charles Carter complaining of Charles Worrell, Frederick County., 2 p.
    - Account, 1756, William Green to Jarvis Hougham., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1756, William Crawford to George Rose., 2 p.
    - Account, 15 March 1756, James Hagin to Matthew Robinson., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1750-7 August 1756, Phelby Anderson, Daniel Johnson, John Lindsey, and William Potter to John Davis., 2 p.
    - Account, June 1755-September 1756, John Laury and Philip Detheridge to William Cuningham., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1757, Philip Babb to James Magill., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1757, Philip Ramith to Exhonor Ramilie., 1 leaf.
    - Deposition, 28 July 1757, Testimony of Daniel McFarne concerning promise of Captain Christopher Gist to pay Thomas McGuire on account of Colonel Grimes. Frederick County., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 26 September 1757, to the sheriff of Frederick County, an attachment requiring the seizure of the estate of John Hamilton in Henry Heth v. John Hamilton., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1757-1758 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Execution, 28 September 1757, to Gerrard Smith, deputized constable of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. for goods of John Hamilton., 2 p.
    - Account, August 1754-February 1757, John Reagan to Robert Worthington., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 28 September 1757, Alexander Woodrow and Mordecai Buckner of Frederick County, to Thomas Speake., 1 leaf.
    - Letter, 31 October 1757, Jarvis Hougham to Mr. West attorney-at-law., 1 leaf.
    - Account, February 1757-November 1757, John Hamilton to Alexander Woodrow., 2 p.
    - Account, 25 May 1756-3 December 1757, William Stewart to Woodrow and Neilson., 2 p.
    - Account, 10 February 1758, Michael Arbeghost to an unknown individual., 1 leaf.
    - Account, March 1758, Mordicai Balson to Henry Churchill., 1 leaf.
    - Account, July 1758, John Lemley to Thomas Langdon., 1 leaf.
    - Account, September 1758, Thomas Colson to Thomas Lindsay., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1759-1760 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Account, 17 February 1759, Thomas Connelly, deceased, to Richard Beckett., 2 p.
    - Bond, 16 June 1759, Israel Potts of Frederick County to Samuel Staensky, welder, of Frederick County., 2 p.
    - Account, 24 October 1759, Samuel Kerr in account with Lenox and Scott., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 16 December 1759, to the sheriff of Prince William County. Fi. Fa. for goods and chattel of John McDonald. Absalom Forsythe v. John McDonald., 2 p.
    - Execution, 6 November 1759, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to seize goods of Jonathan Spault. Richard Fletcher v. Jonathan Spault., 2 p.
    - Execution, 7 March 1760, to any sworn officer of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of James Erwin. Matthew Beasly v. James Erwin., 2 p.
    - Account, 17-20 April 1760, Edward Rogers to James Craik., 2 p.
    - Bond, 7 May 1760, Mary Wood, James Craik, and Gabriel Jones to John Lindsay, Lewis Stephens, William Cox, and John Greenfield., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 29 May 1760, William Connol and Stephen Rollins, both of Frederick County, to Samuel Worthington and John Smith., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 29 May 1760, Stephen Rollins and William Connel, both of Frederick County, to Samuel Worthington and John Smith., 1 leaf, copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1760-1762 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bond, 3 June 1760, Thomas Swearingen, Edward Lucas, and Jacob Van Meter of Frederick County to John Hardin, John Lindsay, William Cocks, and John Sheen., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 6 May 1761, to the coroner of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of John Stewart. Van Swearingen v. John Stewart., 2 p.
    - Account, 6 July 1761-22 December 1761, Elisha Williams in account with Nathaniel Pendleton., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1761-1762, from an unknown individual to John Duncastle., 2 p.
    - Protest, 14 January 1762, John Buchanan of London, merchant, to Richard Oswald and Company concerning bill of exchange from Gilbert Bain to Richard Oswald and Company regarding Richard Barrett., 2 p.
    - Protest, 15 March 1762, Gilbert Bain to Richard Oswald and Company, concerning bill of exchange from Gilbert Bain to Richard Oswald adn Company regarding Richard Barrett., 2 p.
    - Protest, 14 August 1762, Williams and Bellamy of London, merchants, to Gabriel D. Webre, merchant in London, concerning bill of exchange from Richard Barrett to Gabriel D. Webre regarding Messrs. Carlyle and Dalton., 2 p.
    - Execution, 19 August 1762, to the sheriff of James City County, [Virginia]. Ca. Sa. requiring George Jackson Powell to satisfy John Lewis., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 27 September 1762, from Philip Hufman to Thomas Swearingen., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Account, 1762, from an unknown individual to Richard Barrett., 4 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1762-1765 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Account, 1762-1763, Francis McCulloch to an unknown individual., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 11 August 1760-29 January 1763, James Buchanan to B. Bruin., 1 leaf.
    - Commission, 3 March 1763, to John Upshaur and John Lee of Essex County for the examination of Mary Garnett, wife of John Garnett, Jr., of Essex County, regarding deed, 6 February 1763, from John Garnett, Jr., to John Upsham., 2 p.
    - Bond, 10 May 1763, Abraham Hite, Benjamin Kaykendall, and Garret Vanmeter to King George III. Recorded Hampshire County, [(West) Virginia]., 2 p.
    - Account, 25 November 1760-14 June 1763, Francis Maginnis to the estate of William Long, deceased., 1 leaf.
    - Note, 4 December 1764, from James Stroud to an unknown individual., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 6 December 1764, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. for the goods of Joseph Dunn. Judiah Higgins v. Joseph Dunn., 2 p.
    - Execution, 6 December 1764, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach goods of Joseph Dunn. John Burcham v. Joseph Dunn., 2 p.
    - Execution, 14 December 1764, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of John Funk. Martin Funk, James Ireson, and Lewis Stephens v. John Funk., 2 p.
    - Account, 1765, John Graham in account with Andrew Cochran and William Cunningham., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1765-1767 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Execution, 4 March 1765, to any sworn officer or the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach goods of Lawrence Vanbusgararett. Samuel Harrison v. Lawrence Vanbusgararett., 2 p.
    - Account, November 1764-April 1765, Robert Gains to Andrew Cochrane, William Cunninghame, in account with William Reid., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1762-1766, Colonel Adam Stephen to Peter How., 3 p.
    - Indenture, 19 August 1766, binding Patrick Larkin as a servant to Thomas Blood for seven years in return for passage to America., 2 p.
    - Deposition, 20 October 1766, testimony of Mrs. Sarah Fairfax in the action of Anne Gist v. Van Swearingen. Fairfax County., 3 p.
    - Execution, 5 November 1766, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Henry Hardin, Jr., to answer Patrick and William Bogles and Colin Dunlop., 1 leaf.
    - Deed, 1 January 1767, for 450 acres in Frederick County, from Thomas Doncason of Murray County, Scotland, surgeon, to Edward Stevens of Fredericksburg, Spotsylvania County, [Virginia]. Recorded in Frederick County 3 March 1767., 4 p.
    - Execution, 6 [June] 1767, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Henry Hardin to answer Patrick Bogles and Colin Dunlop., 1 leaf, incomplete.
    - Power of attorney, 15 September 1767, John Mitchell, one of the surviving partners of Lenox, Scott, and Company of Fredericksburg, Spotsylvania County, merchants, to Alexander White of Frederick County. Recorded Frederick County 7 November 1767., 2 p.
    - Deed, 12 September 1767, for tracts of land equalling 1020 acres in Frederick County from John Mitchell, one of the surviving partners of Lenox, Scott, and Company of Fredericksburg, merchants, to Bryan Bruin of Winchester, Frederick County. Recorded Frederick County 4 November 1767., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1767-1768 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Bill of exchange, 5 November 1767, Robert Burwell to Robert Cary, concerning Alexander Henderson., 2 p.
    - Account, 1768, William Carlyle to Michael Pyke., 1 leaf.
    - Account, March 1768, Stephen Rawlings to H. Churchill., 1 leaf.
    - Account, March 1768, Martin Funk to H. Churchill., 1 leaf.
    - Bill of sale, 7 November 1767, for one servant woman named Hester Coleman from Samuel Price of Winchester, Frederick County, to Thomas Rutherford of Frederick County. Recorded 2 March 1768., 2 p.
    - Protest, 5 April 1768, Messrs. Robert and Robert Bogle and Scott William Baker to Robert Cary, merchant in London, concerning bill of exchange from Robert Burwell to Robert Cary regarding Alexander Henderson., 3 p.
    - Promissory note, 26 April 1768, from Van Swearingen to Robert Cockburn., 2 p.
    - Account, 26-30 May 1768, James Strother to James Buchanan., 2 p.
    - Account, 29 October 1768, Bryce Hannah to Walter Cunningham., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 4 November 1768, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach the goods and chattel of Henry Hardin, Jr. Patrick and William Bogle and John Dunlop v. Henry Hardin, Jr., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1768-1771 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Lottery ticket, 16 November 1768, Michael Tyke to Ralph Wormeley. Ticket number 1362 in Colonel Bernard Moore's lottery., 1 leaf.
    - Deposition, 2 January 1769, testimony of Mary Prible and John Swan in the action of Joseph Mei v. Philix Hughes. Frederick County., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, April 1769, from Thomas Hatfield to William Brooke., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 17 May 1769, David Griffith to Jacob Hite., 2 p.
    - Commission, 29 September 1770, to Burr Harrison and Matthew Harrison, Gentlemen Justices of Frederick County for the examination of Mary Smith, wife of Wastly Smith, regarding deed, 23 August 1769, from Wastly Smith and Mary Smith to Abraham Brubaker., 2 p.
    - Account, 1770, Richard Griffith to Robert Cockburn., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 3 July 1770, Betty Throckmorton and William Throckmorton to Edmund Pendleton and Peter Lyons, trustees for Colonel Bernard Moore's lottery., 1 leaf.
    - Deed, 1 March 1771, for tract of land in Frederick County from John Neavill of Frederick County to George Fallis of King George County. Recorded Frederick County 5 March 1771., 2 p.
    - Bond, 2 May 1771, Isaac Zane and Alexander White, both of Frederick County, to John Blair., 2 p.
    - Account, 2-4 May 1771, John Blair to Isaac Zane., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1771-1772 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Execution, 6 May 1771, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach goods and chattel of Henry Hardin, Jr. Patrick and William Bogle and Colin Dunlop v. Henry Hardin, Jr., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 13 May 1771, from John Huff to Isaac Zane., 2 p.
    - Execution, 15 May 1771, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Michael Pike to answer Edmund Pendleton and Peter Lyons, trustees for Colonel Bernard Moore's Lottery., 2 p.
    - Account, March-July 1771, George French to Isaac Zane., 2 p.
    - Bond, 21 August 1771, William Drew of Williamsburg to William Lewis of Williamsburg., 1 leaf.
    - Precept, 1 October 1771, James Wood to the sheriff of Frederick County commanding him to bring James Steele before the Justices of the Peace., 1 leaf.
    - Bill of exchange, 7 November 1771, John Throckmorton to Robert Cary, merchant of London, concerning Haldenby Dixon., 1 leaf.
    - Account, July-December 1771, Henry Redmond in account with Isaac Hite., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1772, Isaac Zane to George Rice., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1772, Captain Charles Smith to William Love, and others., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1772 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Bond, 2 March 1772, Jonathan Stout and Isaac Zane to Thomas Rutherford., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 1 April 1772, to any sworn officer of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of George French. Isaac Zane v. George French., 2 p.
    - Bond, 5 May 1772, James Wood and Robert Wood of Frederick County to Arthur Morson and Edward Moore, executors of the will of Dehar Thompson, deceased., 1 leaf.
    - Warrant, 4 June 1772, to the sheriff or any constable of Frederick County for the arrest of James Garner and John McIntire for the shooting of Jeremiah Beale., 2 p.
    - Bond, 11 July 1772, Mann Page and John Page, executors of Robert Page, deceased, and William Eggleston and George Rice of Frederick County to John Elliott., 2 p.
    - Bond, 15 October 1772, John Smith and Jacob Reese of Stafford County to William Love and Company., 2 p.
    - Execution, 28 October 1772, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Attachment for seizure of estate of Jonathan Stout. Isaac Zane v. Jonathan Stout., 2 p.
    - Execution, 4 November 1772, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of Joseph Butler. Benjamin Buler v. Joseph Butler., 2 p.
    - Bond, 4 November 1772, Robert Rutherford of Frederick County to George Mitchell of Fredericksburg, merchant., 2 p.
    - Bond, 25 November 1772, Francis Whiting, Thomas Whiting, and John Perrin of Gloucester County to James Somerville of Fredericksburg, Spotsylvania County., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1773-1774 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Bond, 5 March 1773, Morgan Alexander and Charles Thruston of Frederick County to George Mitchell of Spotsylvania County., 2 p.
    - Execution, 26 March 1773, to any sworn officer of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach estate of Peter Stephens. George Michael Laubinger v. Peter Stephens., 2 p.
    - Bond, 21 April 1773, Jacob Hite of Berkeley County [(West) Virginia], to Charles McEvans of New York, [New York]., 2 p.
    - Deed, 21 April 1773, for land in Donmore (Dunmore, now Shenandoah) County, [Virginia], from John Denton to George Keller, both of Dunmore County., 2 p., incomplete.
    - Execution, 25 October 1773, to the sheriff or any sworn officer of Frederick County. Attachment requiring seizure of estate of Michael Burns. Isaac Zane v. Michael Burns., 2 p.
    - Bond, 6 December 1773, Benjamin Morris and David Wilson of Frederick County to William Pollard and Francis Pollard., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 7 December 1773, James Wood to John Briscoe., 4 p.
    - Bond, 2 March 1774, James Wilson of Frederick County to Charles Yates, surviving partner, Dehar Thompson and Company., 2 p.
    - Bond, 15 March 1774, Francis Willis, Jr., and John Hite of Berkeley County to Alexander Machir., 1 leaf.
    - Answer, 8 June 1774, of Robert Ashley in the action of Robert Ashley v. Argall Tayler., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1774-1777 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Bond, 1 July 1774, Thomas Pool of Gloucester County to James Mills., 2 p.
    - Bond, 25 October 1774, Robert Rutherford of Berkeley County to Joseph Fox of Philadelphia., 4 p.
    - Bond, 21 January 1775, Robert Rutherford to George Fowler., 2 p.
    - Receipt, 16 February 1775, Pruson Bowdoin to Robert Rutherford., 2 p.
    - Bond, 10 March 1775, Thomas Throgmorton [Throckmorton] of Prince William County to James Ritchie and Company., 2 p.
    - Bond, 13 June 1775, Cornelius Livingston of King and Queen County to Richard Teagle., 2 p.
    - Bond, 4 January 1776, Isaac Zane of Frederick County, ironmaster, to William Allason of King George County., 2 p.
    - Bond, 10 January 1776, William Drew, clerk of Berkeley County, to Alexander Purdie and John Dixon of Williamsburg., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 1 September 1776, from William Headley to Messrs. Fisher and Cunningham., 2 p.
    - Bond, 11 January 1777, from an unknown idividual to George Muse of Caroline County., 2 p., incomplete.
  - Legal Papers, 1777-1783 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bond, 2 August 1777, Francis H. Christien and John Catesby Cocke to Elizabeth Flood, William Peachey, and LeRoy Peachey, administrators of the estate of Nicholas Flood, deceased., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 10 August 1778, from William Ball of Prince William County to Charles West of Loudoun County., 1 leaf.
    - Account, October 1778, The Paradire [Paradise?] Plantation to A. and I. Harrison and Company, Thomas Farrer, John Hooke, William Lacey, John Wington and Son., 2 p.
    - Deed, 25 October 1779, for 1380 acres of land and 600 acres of marsh in King and Queen County from John Parke Custis and Eleanor his wife, to James Henry of Accomack County, [Virginia]. Recorded in Williamsburg 26 October 1779., 2 p., copy.
    - receipt, 31 December 1779, George Stricker to Henry Darnall and Benjamin Bradford[?] to an unknown individual., 2 p.
    - Commission, 25 November 1780, to unknown individual for the examination of Judith [Nelson?], wife of Hugh [Nelson?], for right of dower., 1 leaf, incomplete.
    - Receipt, 4 July 1782, J. Wormeley to James Blair., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 1783, Abraham Lindsay to Warner Washington., 1 leaf.
    - Receipts, 3 May 1783, J. M., Jr.; T. B., Jr.; and J. F. M., Jr., to J. Ambler; Joseph Jones, A. Lee, J. M., Jr., to Colonel Bland; and Thadeus Bland, Jr. to [J. Madison?]., 2 p. copies.
    - Promissory note, 15 September 1783, from Andrew Carnegy of Frederick County to William Ball., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1784-1786 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Note, 5 May 1784, Cornelius Livingston and Gabriel Throckmorton to John M. Gill., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 31 August 1784, to the sheriff of Berkeley County. Ca. resp. requiring William Throckmorton to answer Edmund Pendleton and Peter Lyons, trustees for Colonel Bernard Moore's lottery, and administrators of the estate of John Robinson, deceased., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 11 November 1784, from Churchill Gordon, executor of William Purie, to James Gordon., 2 p., incomplete.
    - Promissory note, 7 March 1785, from John Frazer to P. Cassainger., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 29 June 1785, from Thomas Hampton of Frederick County to William Herndon of Culpeper [County, Virginia]., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 31 August 1785, John Wormeley of Virginia to James M. Lingan of Maryland., 2 p., copy.
    - Execution, 6 September 1785, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring James Mercer, executor of Charles Dick, deceased, to answer Catharine Brinker and Frederick Haas, executors of Henry Brinker., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 28 September 1785, from Isaac Zane of Frederick County to Jacob Pugh of Hampshire County., 2 p.
    - Resolution, 1 February 1786, in Congress ordering the renewal of loan office certificates. Signed by William Duer, acting secretary to the Board of Treasury., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 21 February 1786, from an unknown individual to George Cheek., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1786 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bond, 24 February 1786, Isaac Zane and Mordicai Beane of Frederick County to Elioner James of Frederick County., 2 p.
    - Bond, 14 March 1786, Michael Cresap, Ralph Humphrey, Edward McCarty, and William Johnson to Abraham Johnson, John Forman, Isaac Millar, and Marquis Calmes. Recorded in Hampshire County 14 March 1786., 2 p.
    - Bond, 17 April 1786, William Little of Berkeley County to John Bull of Berkeley County., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 17 April 1786, William Little of Berkeley County to John Bull of Berkeley County., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 6 May 1786, Joseph Keller and Isaac Zane of Shenandoah County to Peter Horn of Frederick County., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 10 May 1786, from George Braxton to Doctor Matthew Pope., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 24 June 1786, Fairfax Hancock to Sam[uel] Kercheval., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 24 June 1786, John Mustin of King George County to William Lyles, surviving partner of Lyles and Jackson., 2 p.
    - Bond, 26 June 1786, Richard Baissey of Fauquier County to William Wilson of Alexandria., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 21 September 1786, Simon Cray McMahan of Fauquier County and Fielding Lewis of Frederick County to John Augustine Washington of Westmoreland County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Power of attorney, 16 December 1786, John Murray of New York City and Philip Samson of London, merchants, to Thomas Roberts of America, merchant. Includes account of Lawrence and Morris, merchants in New York, with Murray, Samson and Company, 4 p. and 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1787 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Execution, 20 January 1787, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Fi. Fa. to attach the goods and chattel of Christopher McCannon. Argyle Taylor v. Christopher McCannon., 4 p.
    - Bond, 29 January 1787, Cornelius Livingston of Frederick County to Matthew Wright and Company of Winchester., 2 p.
    - Plea, [21 February 1787], Thomas Garnett complaining of George Eskridge, Frederick County., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 26 May 1787, Gabriel Throckmorton to William Strother of Culpeper [County]., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 21 February 1787, George Eskridge to Thomas Garnett of Richmond County, [Virginia]., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 4 April 1787, Edward McGuire, Edward Snickers, Marquis Calmes, Robert Wood, James Ware, Daniel Morgan, and Burnett Williams to Jacquilin Ambler, Treasurer of Virginia. Recorded in Frederick County 4 April 1787., 2 p.
    - Bond, 1 May 1787, Dorsey Pentacost and [Phil. Pendleton, John Brownley, M. Thurston, John Thurston, and John Cordell] to George Rootes of Berkeley County., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 11 October 1787, Michael Cresap, sheriff of Hampshire [County], Samuel Dw, Ralph Humphreys, and Ovid McCrackin to Jaquilin Ambler, Treasurer of Virginia. Recorded in Hampshire County 11 October 1787., 2 p. copy.
    - Bond, 11 October 1787, Michael Cresap, sheriff of Hampshire [County], Samuel Dw, Ralph Humphreys, and Ovid McCrackin to Jaquilin Ambler, Treasurer of Virginia. Recorded in Hampshire County 11 October 1787., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 11 October 1787, Michael Cresap, sheriff of Hampshire [County], Samuel Dw, Ralph Humphreys, and Ovid McCrackin to Jaquilin Ambler, Treasurer of Virginia. Recorded in Hampshire County 11 October 1787., 2 p. copy.
    - Bond, 11 October 1787, Michael Cresap, sheriff of Hampshire [County], Samuel Dw, Ralph Humphreys, and Ovid McCrackin to Jaquilin Ambler, Treasurer of Virginia. Recorded in Hampshire County 11 October 1787., 2 p. copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1787-1789 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Bond, 21 December 1787, William Newton and John Bronaugh of Alexandria, Fairfax County, to David Galloway, Jr., of Frederick County., 2 leaves.
    - Promissory note, 29 February 1788, from Edward Tiffin to John Mark and Company., 2 p., copy.
    - Deposition, 16 October 1788, Samuel Beale before P. Barraud in Williamsburg., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 12 December 1787, from Simeon Haines to John Griffith., 2 p.
    - Order, 8 December 1788, George Braxton to Robert Fleming concerning Charles Irving., 2 p.
    - Deed, 12 December 1788, for 478 acres in Frederick County from Hugh Nelson of Yorktown to James Ware of Frederick County. Recorded 7 July 1789., 4 p.
    - Commission, 9 February 1789, to John Peyton as clerk to the court composed of the counties of Frederick, Berkeley, Hampshire, Hardy, and Shenandoah. Signed by J. Mercer, Richard Parker, Edmund Winston, Richard Cary, James Henry, John Tyler, and Cuthbert Bullitt., 1 leaf.